A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1972-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1972-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.751
This collection consists of 29,400 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was forwarded to the library on 14 July 1975.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of general and committee files.
Contents List
- Series I: General Records
  - "A-Al" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - "An - Az" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Academic Deans 1972-1973 (Box 1)
  - Admissions - General 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - "A - Z" 1972-1973 (Box 2)
  - Admissions - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Air Force ROTC 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni - Medical 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Charlottesville, Albemarle Chapter 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Lynchburg Chapter 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Maryland Chapter 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Association - Wilmington Chapter 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Day 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Fund 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - Alumni News 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - American Association of University Professors 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education 1972-1973 (Box 3)
  - American Council on Education - Annual Report, 1971 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education - A Fact Book on Higher Education 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education - A Report of the Treasurer 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - American Council on Education - Higher Education and National Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Annual Report - President's 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Annual Reports 1972-1973 (Box 4)
  - Applications for Positions - "A - M" 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Applications for Positions - "N - Z" 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Architecture - General 1972-1973 (Box 5)
  - Army - General 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Army - ROTC 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Army - Judge Advocate's General (J.A.G.) School 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Art - General 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Art - Bayly Museum 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Art - Graduate Institute of the History of Art in Washington 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Art Commission 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Asian Studies Consortium 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Colleges 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Colleges - Membership Committee 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Universities 1972-1973 (Box 6)
  - Association of American Universities - Council on Federal Relations 1972-1973 (Box 7)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Astronomy 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - General 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - Basketball 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - Football 1972-1973 (Box 8)
  - Athletics - Finances 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - ACC 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Invitations to Games 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, South Carolina - 9 September 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, V. P. I. - 16 September 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, West Virginia - 23 September 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Duke - 30 September 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Vanderbilt - 7 October 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Commonwealth Day - 14 October 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, North Carolina - 11 November 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Football, Wake Forest - 18 November 1972 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Basketball, North Carolina - 24 February 1973 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - NCAA 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Atlantic Council of United States 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Athletics - Rowing Team 1972-1973 (Box 9)
  - Attorney General (State) 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Atomic Energy Commission 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Audit Reports 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - "B - Bm" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - "Bn - Bz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 10)
  - Biology - General 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Biology - Mountain Lake 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Budget Office - General 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Budget Director 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Budget Office - Capital Outlay 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds - General 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Buildings and Grounds - Progress Reports 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Bursar 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Business and Finance 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Business Manager 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - "Ca - Ck" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 12)
  - "Cl - Cz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 12)
  - Calendar of Events 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Cavalier Daily 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Center for Advanced Studies 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Center for the Study of science, Technology and Public Policy 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Chemistry - General 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Civil Defense 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Civil Rights 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Classics 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - Clinch Valley College - General 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1972-1973 (Box 13)
  - College Entrance Examination Board 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - General 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Comptroller (State) 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Comptroller (University) 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Computer Center 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Consortium for Continuing Higher Education in Northern Virginia 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Consultative Resource Center on School Desegregation at U.Va. 1972-1973 (Box 14)
  - Continuing Education - General 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education - Eastern Shore 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education - Hampton Roads Center 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education - Madison Center 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education - Richmond Center 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education - Roanoke Center 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education - Southwest Virginia Center 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Continuing Education - Virginia High School League 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Center for Continuing Education in Northern Virginia 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Council of Presidents 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Counsel to President for Special Developments 1972-1973 (Box 15)
  - Council of Southern Universities (see also Southern Fellowship) 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - "Da - De" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - "Df - Dz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Danforth Foundation 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Data Processing 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Development Office 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - "E" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Economics 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Education - General 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Endowment Fund 1972-1973 (Box 17)
  - Engineering and Applied Science 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Engineering and Buildings 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - English 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Enrollment 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Environmental Sciences 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - "F" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Faculty - General 1972-1973 (Box 18)
  - Faculty Orientation and Reception 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - General 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Committees of 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Federal Executive Institute 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Federal Executive Institute - National Advisory Board 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - General 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Bayly-Tiffany 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Cross 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Dupont Regional 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Fulbright 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Hoxton 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Love 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships - Rhodes 1972-1973 (Box 20)
  - Finals 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - Ford Foundation 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - Founder's Day 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - French Literature and General Linguistics 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - "G" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - General Assembly 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - George Mason College 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Germanic Literature 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Gifts and Grants - Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office - Executive Orders 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office - Administration 1972-1973 (Box 23)
  - Governor's Office - Education 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Governor's Advisory Board - Tour, 22 May 1973 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Graduate Business Sponsors 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Graphics 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Growth 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Guggenheim Foundation 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - "H" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Higher Education Act - 1965 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Highway Department 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - History 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Honor System and Honor Committee 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Housing 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Information Services 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Institute of Current World Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Institute of Government 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Institutional Analysis 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - International Students 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - B 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - C 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - D 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - F 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - G 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - H 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - M 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - N 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - P 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - R 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - S 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - T 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - U 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - V 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Invitations - W 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - "J" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Jefferson, Thomas 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1972-1973 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Monthly Reports 1972-1973 (Box 28)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation - Board Minutes 1972-1973 (Box 28)
  - Jefferson Society 1972-1973 (Box 28)
  - Judiciary Committee 1972-1973 (Box 28)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 28)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 28)
  - Law - General 1972-1973 (Box 28)
  - Law Journal Reprints 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Law Admissions, "A - Z" 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Law - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Law Enforcement Education Program (LEEP) 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Lectures 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Legal Advisor 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Legal Estates 1972-1973 (Box 29)
  - Council on Library Resources 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - Library Associates 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - Library - General 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous - General 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - McGregor Fund 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - McIntire Fund 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - "Ma - Me" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 30)
  - "Mi - Mz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Madison Hall 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Markle Foundation 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Mary Washington College 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Mathematics 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Marine Science 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Medical Center - General 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Medical School - Admissions 1972-1973 (Box 31)
  - Medical Center - Health Sciences 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Medical School 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Hospital 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Monthly Statistical Reports 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Nursing 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Operating Budget and Reports 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Medical Center - Reports on Current Operations 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Monticello - Wildflowers of Virginia 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - Music 1972-1973 (Box 32)
  - "Na" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 33)
  - "Ne - Nz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 33)
  - NASA 1972-1973 (Box 33)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) 1972-1973 (Box 33)
  - NASULGC - Circular Letters 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - NASULGC - Proceedings of the 85th Annual Convention 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - NASULGC - Membership Committee 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - NASULGC - Office of Executive Director 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - NASULGC - International Letters 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - NASULGC - Office of Institutional Research, For Your Information 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - NASULGC - Office of Advancement of Public Negro Colleges 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - National Commission on Accrediting 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - National Historical Publications Commission 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - National Medal of Science 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - National Science Foundation 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - National Science Foundation - Advisory Committee for Institutional Relations 1972-1973 (Box 34)
  - National Science Foundation - Federal Funds for Academic Science, 1970 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - National Science Foundation - Institutional Grants for Science 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - National Science Foundation - Advisory Committee Memo 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - National Trust for Historic Preservation 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - National War College 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Navy - General 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Navy - ROTC 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Naval War College 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Navy League of the United States 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Newcomen Society 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Newspaper Clippings 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Oceanic Educational Foundation 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Office Invoices 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - Office Travel 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - "P - Ph" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - "Pi - Pz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - Parking and Transit 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - Personnel - General 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Personnel - Employee Relations 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Philosophy 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Physics - General 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Physics - Personnel 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Planning Division (State) 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Planning Department 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Project Status Reports 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Provost 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Psychology 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - Public Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - Purchasing 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - Questionnaires and Inquiries 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - Raven Society 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - Recommendations - "A - Z" 1972-1973 (Box 39)
  - Registrar 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - Registrar - Student Reports 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - Rehabilitation Center 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - Religious Studies 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - ROTC 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - "S - Sl" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - "Sm - Sz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 40)
  - Salaries 1972-1973 (Box 41)
  - Security Department 1972-1973 (Box 41)
  - Senate (University) 1972-1973 (Box 41)
  - Seven Society 1972-1973 (Box 41)
  - Slavic Literature 1972-1973 (Box 41)
  - Spanish and Portuguese Literature 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Sociology and Anthropology 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Southern University Conference 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Special Programs 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Special Programs - ACTION 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Speech and Drama 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Speech Pathology and Audiology 1972-1973 (Box 42)
  - Presentation to the State Council of Higher Education - Biennial Visit, 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - 7-Sep-72 (Box 43)
  - State Board of Education 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Speeches by the President for the Current Year 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - Sponsored Programs 1972-1973 (Box 43)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1972-1973 (Box 44)
  - State Council of Higher Education 1972-1973 (Box 45)
  - State Department of Higher Education 1972-1973 (Box 45)
  - Student Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 45)
  - Student Affairs - Happy Day 1972-1973 (Box 45)
  - Student Council 1972-1973 (Box 45)
  - Student Council - Minutes of Meetings 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Student Legal Forum 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Student Health Department 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Summer Finals 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - Summer Session 1972-1973 (Box 46)
  - "T" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 47)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1972-1973 (Box 47)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1972-1973 (Box 47)
  - Treasurer (University) 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - Treasurer (State) 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - Tuition and Fees 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - Tutoring Program for First Year Students 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - United States Department of Agriculture 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - United States Congress 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - United States Department of Defense 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - United States Department of Health, Education, and Welfare 1972-1973 (Box 48)
  - United States Naval Academy 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - United States Department of State 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Center in Virginia 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Editor 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Housing - General 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Press of Virginia 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Printing Office 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Registrar 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Research Associates 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - University Union 1972-1973 (Box 49)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Virginia Commission on Higher Education Facilities 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Virginia Historical Society 1972-1973 (Box 50)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - Virginia Weekly 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - "Wa - Wh" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - "Wi - Wz" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 51)
  - Water Resources 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - "X - Y - Z" Miscellaneous 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - Visitors 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - Visitors - Buildings and Grounds 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - Visitors - Educational Policy Committee 1972-1973 (Box 52)
  - Visitors - Executive Committee 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Finance Committee 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Library Committee 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Health Sciences Committee 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Medical Committee 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Docket, 13 October 1972 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 13 October 1972 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Docket, 8 December 1972 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 8 December 1972 1972-1973 (Box 53)
  - Visitors - Docket, 2 February 1973 1972-1973 (Box 54)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 2 February 1973 1972-1973 (Box 54)
  - Visitors - Docket, 6 April 1973 1972-1973 (Box 54)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 6 April 1973 1972-1973 (Box 54)
  - Visitors - Docket, 1 June 1973 1972-1973 (Box 54)
  - Visitors - Minutes, 1 June 1973 1972-1973 (Box 54)
- Series II: University Committees, 1972-1973
  - Special Committee: Academic Calendar 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Administrative Committees 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Special Committee: New Physics Building 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Special Committee: Advisory Planning Committee for Undergraduate Women 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Ad hoc Committee: Search for Vice President for Student Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Ad hoc Committee: Search for Dean of Engineering School 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Ad hoc Committee: Search for Dean of School of Nursing 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Ad hoc Committee: Search for successor to Weldon Cooper 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Academic Computing Committee 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Admissions Committee 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Arboretum Committee 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Architectural Advisory Committee 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Athletic Advisory Council 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Calendar and Scheduling Committee 1972-1973 (Box 55)
  - Catalogue Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Danforth Fellowships Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Data Process9ng Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Environment Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Fulbright Grants Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Gwathmey Award Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Health Sciences Policy Board Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Housing Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Institutional Analysis Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Lectures - Special 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Coin Medal Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Library Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Master Plan Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Names Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Processions Committee 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Committee on Public Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 56)
  - Committee on Public Affairs 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Public Occasions Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Radiation Safety Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Records Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Registration Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Rhodes Scholarships Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - ROTC Affairs Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Security and General Safety Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Student Activities Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Student Health Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Summer Grants Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Traffic Appeals Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Traffic and Parking Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - University Union Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)
  - Virginia Status of University Students Committee 1972-1973 (Box 57)